Those unyielding prayers - you have been praying, fasting -
as from today, you can do all things through Christ Jesus who strengthens you.
Say, I can do all things through Christ Jesus who strengthens me,
in the name of Jesus!
Not that you deserve it but Jesus anoints those who He chooses to anoint.
He chose you today! You are a chosen one!
Tell your neighbour: I don't deserve it; He decided to choose me.
He chooses whom He chooses; He loves whom He loves.
I am anointed today, in the name of Jesus!
Stretch your hand forward!
Begin to lay your hand right now -
the anointed hand, the right hand of God!
Those who are with us, those who are for us, pray with us!
Stretch your hand! You will feel the vibration, presence of God
as it should be, by divine will, in Jesus' name!
Say, as it should be, by divine will!
Something divine cannot be ordinary.
If it were ordinary, you are not qualified.
Tell your neighbour: Something divine cannot be ordinary.
If it were ordinary, if it were your brother, if it were T.B. Joshua
that is giving it, he may not give me.
But God chooses as He wills.
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Every hand that participated, be anointed!
Every tongue that participated, be anointed!
The right hand of God is power!
Say, the right hand of God is power!
Say, tongue!
I have received a tongue to loose and bind, in the name of Jesus!
As the mass prayer was conducted by Prophet T.B. Joshua,
thousands of people received instant healing.
One particular lady - miraculously the Holy Spirit flushed out of her body a fibroid,
while praying along with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
When the power of God is present, healing is like breathing,
deliverance is like breathing and breakthrough is like breathing.
The age of miracles has not passed.
The miracle-worker is still alive.
His name is Jesus Christ.
Viewers all over the world, let's watch.
Look at the screen of your television.
This is the woman who has come today with the problem of multiple fibroids.
While the prayer was going on by the man of God, the fibroids started coming out of her body.
Fibroid Growths Bursting
Whatever that is not of God, when you leave from here and go to the restroom,
you will begin to defecate what is not part of your life.
What is the trouble in your business?
You will use your mouth to loose and to bind it.
Your finances will be reinstated.
Your marriage will be restructured.
Thank You, Lord.
I'm happy for your life.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, Changing the World.